<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ghosts-N-Whatever</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="title_activity_lobby">LobbyActivity</string>

    <string name="ghost_description">As a Ghost, your main objective is to... "Borrow" Souls from the local village, and return these souls to your family Crypt.
        For Each soul delivered we will reward you with one afterlife token to be use in our afterlife-gift-shop. However, be aware! There are others out there trying to get to you.
        If a Ghost Hunter traps you while you are entering your Crypt, or if he surprises you while delivering a soul, he will capture your essence.
        Graverobbers may also come to your family crypt and steal from you your mortal remains.
        Because of the massive amounts of paperwork these unfortunate events generates, mannagement has decided to deduct tokens from the victime of a Ghost Hunting or graverobbing.
        If you however scare of Ghost Hunters or Graverobbers lingeringer in your Family Crypt, by arriving after a them, you will be rewared a complemetary token for "Teaching them not to mess with the deseased"
        You now know what you need in order to succeed in the afterlife, so go out there, earn tokens and grab yourself a T-shirt, or maby even a hat!
    </string>
    <string name="graverobber_description">Greetings fellow Renovation Employee! Others may call us Graverobbers, but thats just because they do not understand the true values of recycling.
        Our job is to visit crypts of the departed an "relieve" them of their worldy possesions, seeing as they do not need them anymore.
        We have contacts in the local village, who are willing to purchace these items from you, and this is how we make a proffit.
        Take care when visiting a crypt, however. If a Ghost or Ghost Hunter is residing in the crypt when you enter, or if you are supprised by a Ghost or Ghost Hunter, you will be frozen in fear, or arrested, taking you out of the game for some time.
        The Ghost Hunters leave traps to capture the ghosts. These are easy to spot for us Graverobb.. i mean Renovation Emploees, and if they are delivered to the village, they can bring in some good bucks!
        That is the basics of our job, so take care, and start making a living as a Graverobber! Whops...
    </string>
    <string name="ghosthunter_description">Calling all Ghost Hunters! The local villiage is in dire need of your help, as Ghosts and Graverobbers are at large.
        Your assignment will be to buy traps from the village and setting them up in crypts. when a Gost is caught, you can deliver it back at the village for a reward, and resuply traps for more capture.
        Graverobbers may seek to profit from your traps and disarm them for proffit. If you catch them in the act, or while they rob a crypt, you can arrest them, and deliver them to the village for a reward.
        Other than trapping a crypt, you can surprise a Ghost, and collect it for delivery to the village.
        If you however are cought by a Gost while planting a trap, you will be knocked out for some time and will lose your trap.
        The nights ar getting darker and longer, and we need your help Ghost Hunter, to save us from our impending doom!
    </string>

</resources>
